

ROVENSAN IGLESIAS





irobhome20@gmail.com



Cuenca Batangas, **Philippines**

SKILLS T



- **Phyton** programming language
- **IT Service** Management with ITIL 4 **Foundation**
- Microsoft excel, word and PowerPoint.
- Sales and Customer Service.

LANGUAGE



- **English**
- **Tagalog**
- Hangul

PROFILE

Experienced Application Support Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in logistics and supply chain industry, skilled in Microsoft word, Microsoft excel and Power point. Also experienced and skilled in Logistic management, Supply chain management, Service now tool, customer support, system support, and Python programming. Strong information technology professional.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES



Tata Consultancy Services

Application Support - 2015 to Present

Responsible for user access management (user access creation, deactivation and reactivation) also responsible for troubleshooting, configuration, and deployment of all kinds of system enhancements that increase efficiency, and smooth operational processes. Responsible to coordinate with internal and External Vendors for reporting, business entity and location set-up, fixing and enhancement to fulfil the business needs and end-user satisfaction.

Global learning Support

Quality Analyst - November 2014 to December 2015

Outlines quality assurance procedures and policies · Oversees implementation of quality assurance procedures and involves monitoring and assessing customer interactions and maintaining consistent compliance with internal and external regulations.

Magellan Solutions

Quality Assurance Specialist - September 2012 to October 2014

Responsible for listening to the verification part of the call. Validates the quality of the verification part and dispose the sales appropriately by following the standards set by the department.

Monitors and evaluates the quality of the verification part of the call done by the agent following the verification process standardize by the department.

- Enters/Encodes specific data needed.
- Follows proper standard procedures/guidelines set by the department.

EDUCATION



AMA University – AMAOED

Bachelor of science and Business administration major in Management information System.

TRAININGS -



Python Programming – MST Connect

IT Service Management with ITIL V4 Foundation full training – Udemy.